<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nikiforos Pittaras</title>
    <link>https://npit.gitlab.io/website/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Nikiforos Pittaras</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2020. All rights reserved.</copyright><atom:link href="https://npit.gitlab.io/website/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Code</title>
      <link>https://npit.gitlab.io/website/code/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 18:26:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://npit.gitlab.io/website/code/</guid>
      <description>Software I developed, contribute to or mantain  A video classification wrapper in python3 and tensorflow (github). The bde event detection module (github) and its corresponding docker image (github, docker hub). An text classification with semantic information module(github).  Software I use and like Productivity  Man pages for human beings: cheat, tldr and how2. RSI-prevention with good typing and modal editing with vim. Vimify browser with cVim and wasavi. Editor war stalemate: spacemacs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>https://npit.gitlab.io/website/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 17:37:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://npit.gitlab.io/website/links/</guid>
      <description>Math  3Blue1Brown Numberphile Mathologer Spurious Correlations  Physics  PBS Spacetime Sixty Symbols  AI Safety  Robert Miles Universal Paperclips  Gamedev  Godot Engine  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://npit.gitlab.io/website/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://npit.gitlab.io/website/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a computer scientist currently pursuing my PhD in Machine Learning and working as a research associate in the Institute of Informatics and Telecommunications in NCSR Demokritos.
You can get a pdf of my detailed cv in English (Updated 3-2021).
Alternatively, check out a tl;dr version below.
Education   PhD in machine learning, from the Informatics and Telecommunications department (DIT) of the National and Kapodistrian University of Athens (NKUA), co-supervised by the Institute of Informatics and Telecommunications (IIT) of the National Center for Scientific Research Demokritos (NCSRD), funded by the St.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
