<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About on Nikiforos Pittaras</title>
    <link>https://npit.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About on Nikiforos Pittaras</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2020. All rights reserved.</copyright><atom:link href="https://npit.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AGI Safety Fundamentals Course 2022 project</title>
      <link>https://npit.github.io/agisf2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 17:37:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://npit.github.io/agisf2022/</guid>
      <description>In the 2022 AGI Safety Fundamentals course I worked on toy investigations on deceptively aligned agents in a toy environment.
You can find relevant code, results and ideas for future work / extensions in this gitlab repository.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AI Safety Camp 2022 project</title>
      <link>https://npit.github.io/aisc6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 17:37:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://npit.github.io/aisc6/</guid>
      <description>In AI Safety Camp 2022 I worked on learning and penalizing betrayal in agent communications in an RL setting. A workshop paper describing research work and empirical outcomes can be found here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://npit.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://npit.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Journals N. Pittaras, G. Giannakopoulos, G. Papadakis, V. Karkaletsis,&amp;ldquo;Text classification with semantically enriched word embeddings&amp;rdquo;, JNLE Special Issue: Informing Neural Architectures for NLP with Linguistic and background Knowledge, 2020 📄 F. Markatopoulou, V. Mezaris, N. Pittaras, I. Patras, &amp;ldquo;Local Features and a Two-Layer Stacking Architecture for Semantic Concept Detection in Video&amp;rdquo;, IEEE TETC, 2015 📄 . Books N. Pittaras, S. Montanelli, G. Giannakopoulos, A. Ferrara, V. Karkaletsis, &amp;ldquo;Crowdsourcing in Single-document Summary Evaluation: the Argo Way&amp;rdquo;, Multilingual Text Analysis: Challenges, Models &amp;amp; Approaches, World Scientific Publishers, 2020 📄</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code</title>
      <link>https://npit.github.io/code/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 18:26:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://npit.github.io/code/</guid>
      <description>Software I use and like Productivity Man pages for human beings: cheat, tldr and how2. RSI-prevention with good typing and modal editing with vim. Vimify browser with vimvixen, cVim and wasavi. Editor war stalemate: spacemacs. Omni-present terminal with dolphin or yakuake F-key magic. Terminal multiplexing with tmux. Screenshot goodness with flameshot. Leisure Terminal youtube player: mps-youtube </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>https://npit.github.io/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 17:37:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://npit.github.io/links/</guid>
      <description>Math 3Blue1Brown Numberphile Mathologer Spurious Correlations CS The missing semester lectures Physics PBS Spacetime Sixty Symbols AI &amp;amp; Machine Learning The bitter lesson Distill AI Safety lesswrong Robert Miles Universal Paperclips Gamedev Godot Engine </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://npit.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://npit.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a Machine Learning scientist, currently working in different ML Research and Engineering roles in multiple domains, including Argument Mining, Multimodal Neurodegenerative Disease Prediction, AI Safety and Alignment.
You can get a short (updated 02-2023) and a long (out of date, but with uni courses / projects) version of my CV.
Alternatively, check out a tl;dr version below.
Education PhD in machine learning, from the Informatics and Telecommunications department (DIT) of the University of Athens (UoA), co-supervised by the Institute of Informatics and Telecommunications (IIT) of the National Center for Scientific Research Demokritos (NCSRD) , funded by the St.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
